Logan Natysin

J (703) 541 9869 Inatysin@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/logan-natysin ⊕ https://lnatysin.github.io

Summary

Software Engineer with 4 years of experience in designing, creating, testing and implementing various software applications. Skilled at working with Python, Java, C, and SQL. Uses these skill to contribute in a collaborative team environment, while contributing to an organization's success in delivering top quality solutions to clients by creating the best user experience.

Education

Virginia Polytechnic Institute & State University

B.S. Computer Science

Battlefield High School

Dec. 2024

Current GPA: 3.55/4.0 June 2021

GPA: 4.58/4.0

Coursework

Courses: Intro to Artificial Intelligence, Data Structures & Algorithms, Computer Systems, Discrete Math, Linear Algebra, Calculus, Physics, Probability & Statistics

Awards: Dean's Honor List (4x), Varsity Golf Team Captain

Skills

Languages: Java, Python, C, SQL

Tools: Git/GitHub, Docker, Unix Shell, VS Code, Eclipse, PyCharm, Overleaf, MATLAB, Microsoft Office Software

Projects

Personal Website | HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git/GitHub, VS Code

Mar. 2024

- Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript to build a personal website to display completed projects. Website is deployed on GitHub pages
- · https://lnatysin.github.io

Pacman Al | Python, Git/GitHub, PyCharm, Al

Feb. 2024

- · Used various AI search algorithms to solve different mazes in Pacman that ranged from easy to complex
- The different search algorithms used were Depth First Search, Breadth First Search, Uniform Cost Search, and A* Search

Personal Web Server | C, HTTP, TCP, Git, Unix Shell, VS Code

Nov. 2023

- Developed and built a personal web server that used HTTP and TCP protocols
- · Supports multithreading for multiple clients, user authentication, video streaming, and more

Experience

$\textbf{Noblis-Reston, VA} \mid \textit{Autonomous Systems Intern}$

Jun. 2024 - Aug. 2024

- Developed and modified a distributed asynchronous network application for autonomous vehicles.
- Designed and created a system of trust within the network of vehicles to increase the efficiency of task completion within the network.
- Designed and created a robust system for assigning tasks within the network based on trust and availability of the autonomous vehicles.
- These distributed systems are now able to work with or without communication, making them more robust and efficient.
- Created a simulation using docker to simulate real world communication between autonomous vehicles over TCP connections.
- Created a unique identity service for autonomous vehicles using SSH keys to encode and decode messages.
- Tools/Skills Used: Python, SQL, Docker, Git/GitHub, TCP networking, Multi-Threading, Robot Operating Systems

Stonewall Golf Club - Gainesville, VA | Starter/Cart Attendant

Jun. 2021 - May 2024

- Improve and strengthen customer service skills through constant customer interaction.
- Time management, troubleshooting, and quick thinking were frequently required to keep the golfers efficiently moving through the course, leading to a better customer experience.

Kappa Delta Rho | Pontifex and Service Chairman

Feb. 2023 - Present

- Founding member of Gamma Beta chapter at Virginia Tech
- Pontifex for Kappa Delta Rho (KDR) at Virginia Tech. In charge of levying fines and brother conduct. Head of the A-Board which dealt with brotherhood conduct
- Service chairman for Kappa Delta Rho (KDR) at Virginia Tech. Organize and plan all community service opportunities for KDR fraternity. Track all community service projects and completion hours for members